[VIDEO GAME PLAYING]
Ha-ha. Eat my dust,
racially stereotypical plumber.
(Sheldon:)That's not fair.
I got stuck behind a tree.
(Raj:)And a cow and a penguin.
(Raj:)Face it, dude, whether it's a real car
or a virtual cartoon car, you can't drive.
(Sheldon:)-Just need a little more practice.
-What you need is cheat codes...
...motor skills and a genie
who grants wishes...
(Raj:)...to little boys
who suck at "Mario Kart."
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)Sheldon,
can I talk to you for a second?
(Sheldon:)It's not about shoes, is it?
(Bernadette:)I don't think
I could go through that again.
(Sheldon:)-It's not about shoes.
-Then speak.
(Penny:)-Um, actually, can we do it in private?
-All right.
(Sheldon:)Go away.
(Sheldon:)I agree, it's rude,
but she asked for privacy.
(Penny:)Thanks, Raj.
Okay, so here's the thing.